Two things, notice you, should we break the achieves to start with?
I get thrown out of that, so the other idea that we can laugh together in your presence here,
and know that you're going to help.
I highly thank you for these chiefs back, and that's his surgery, what will.
Lord, watch a group each person, which, for us today,
with the ones that have every decision to make,
help them win the decision to stop the ailment of the holiday.
I just ask that you will continue to take care of our town, and thank you for it.
And I thank you for these people tonight who are serving as many ways.
And wisdom to the patients.
Jesus, say, we break.
There.
I believe in student life at the United States of America,
and to the Republic for which it stands,
on the nation.
There are individual liberty and justice for all.
I believe in the people of the people of the United States of America,
and the process of making an impact on the women's age.
At the age of 26 and 27,
by the Pacific Ocean.
Of course, that means they're five percent.
They're five percent.
They're six percent.
They're two percent.
They're seven percent.
They're six percent.
So that's a different kind of behavior.
We have VA, the explainings, and the background of this particular invoice, the ocean
room between the modeling.
More importantly, to kind of give you the background when we try to share the numbers,
and sometimes that one is called, so you want to see where we're at, and what we've
budgeted, and how much we've suspended today.
Today, I would like to add a couple of different thousand, which kind of gives that
budget.
And what I really has, the 535,000, 2700,000 remaining, including this 12,580,
this would put to total expenses this year, and 2700,000, so well in the budget
of milk.
And obviously, it's actually actually an amazing job.
For the city, we've got a lot of work on their plate this year.
So we're going to go back to an open experience in the next slide, and we're going to
be to address the potential in the activity that's in contact.
This payment for this world is in the existing content, but we're only going to even have
a thousand dollars in there for people to come.
Where's the data going to go for this, is this just for engineers?
So it's going to be published anywhere in the data that they have in the morning.
So the data that they have from the modeling work will be published.
Now, I'm asking you if it will be published.
Well, it will be available for the public, I guess, in some moments.
Yeah?
I would assume it will be, primarily, because it will be published.
But you can put it into the focus on the integration of the federal website.
We said it will be available.
I don't know how much I'll agree.
I understand all of this.
And now it's going to be my next question.
The beginning of the published, and I'm going to turn into a few more
in what I mentioned.
We will have, in fact, a lot of this that we are going to be discussing a couple of weeks
of capital.
So we'll be discussing a lot of the models.
Well, as I'm not information, you're available for that.
What any of them that is going to be done today, because there's still some
modeling that's going to be produced.
But modeling that has to be done today, we'll be discussing
if it will also discuss what modeling we're going to do.
And so when you talk about modeling, you're talking about the effects
and the levels of the river, as it affects our areas of the river.
If we were software, modeling software, we would be able to place points for
the modeling software that we're going to do today.
What effects there would be?
in the surrounding areas, being the river itself,
because elevations, subterpations.
So I mean, increased lake levels equals x.
You have a question on the left?
Megamotion Hitchcock.
All right.
Is that possible?
No, no, no, no.
No.
Is that correct?
No, no, no.
Not in.
Check your deck contract.
C18, that's 47 extensions.
This was year 22, 23 in the mountains.
39,000, six hundred and eight dollars.
Also, as I mentioned just before, with the voice being approved
for the $5,000 by the lady, about the only $1,000 in the existing $50,000
contract that was approved this year, we've been working extensively with tetrotech,
this fiscal year, being from July to the last year of the calendar year.
And based on the submittals and analysis system done,
it's called a realizing thing that you're trying to report.
It's just taken significantly more effort in disbanding,
and so we've fallen through that contract, we've worked it in disbanded.
We also have remaining, we know, the next five months that will continue to be working with
tetrotech and there is a technical support that will be needed.
Again, the concept of co-ordinating and realizing it, including additional hydrologans,
and sedimentation transport modeling, really, you're right,
a summary of the board of the year in the eight studies,
and fifth and fifth analysis, that will be submitted for March of this year,
as well as public meetings that I've been having here in a couple of weeks,
February 16th, November 10th, there, we've set down and actually really sharpened our pencil
to make sure we were being disciplined, which was possible, and they were great.
We literally got in and added up everything we've costed,
and we knew we would have to remain part of this this week here.
It's total 30,000, 600,000, they've polished it, so that was exactly the big questions
in just a moment.
We added to their existing contract this year, 39,600,000, so that's the contract we did.
So, of course, they've been doing the building, they've been doing additional new voices,
they've been remainder of this, but where's that money coming from?
So, it's part of that same budget.
That was the second year in the fifth, so we were still well within that budget,
we'll be able to do a bunch of new things.
I think we'll get a question from you to that.
I think we're going to come in and shy of that.
Unless there is a lot of work that has to be done between now and March,
but we're probably going to see it pretty clever.
Actually, let's see quite a little effort to get in to March.
We're just going to drop that off a little bit by the middle of the summer,
so we're going to spike it in at all times.
So, I think the effort remaining in this fiscal year will not spike in the summer.
And if that's the case, we'll carry that away.
What's the target date for this real ICDB plan?
Close.
There's a two-par up-to-par out.
Like the deadline for a direct, for GRDA and the interest in the ICDB plan.
I think the life of our health card is 26.
Right.
So that's not good.
It could roll the extended again.
Actually, we're passed to that date.
We're going to extend it.
Yes.
So the original date was back.
We were going to continue on.
So it's then extended to 0.05.
And it did it to begin.
I think the longest that any one has gone was like 30 years.
They operated into this extension.
That's where to go back.
But it shows it is possibly.
And why did they extend it?
I'm quite in 30 extend this out.
You got this stuff in the trade.
But primarily, there are a lot of issues about things.
They've been done by the year.
And we're going to work appropriately.
And we're still arguing sometimes.
We're going to list a thing about this.
It's going to draw out.
The good news is, for it to be requiring that the appropriate thing,
is that we have the appropriate thing.
We're going to work as a question.
And we're going to work as a question.
The last time we were going to work as a question.
I might have been with this.
But it would be pretty simple.
And as I'm going to say, there's something to the right.
We have a bit of a day.
We're going to go back to the last.
And we're going to do that.
I'll say that the test of tech studies that they do are very important in your licensing.
The government's study, the government's transport study, and something that the GRAA said was not happening.
And with these services, the studies they could prove that it's happening.
So those are big for us, and when the park gets those, they turn around and go,
but the show ended up happens, here's the sign of the pandemic, why are you showing us how.
So these studies are the building for paying off, not only for us, but also for the civil case.
And when he comes on the 16th, as Brian said earlier, we were in discussion,
but I told him, you're going to have to explain this and let him start,
because you start talking all these decades, that we're supposed to do what he's talking about in a shaman.
Including me, so you're going to have to explain this to everybody in our stand.
So he's working hard to make sure that's why he's playing on the 16th.
Do we know those as far as who will give me a tending that from professional perspective?
When we're going to have a DWT, we'll be represented two in this case,
and we'll check to the DWT, and my child comes out here.
Council of the United Mayor, you there, I'll be there, very warm.
We can find in a civil aviation show howling was occurring in his division of tribes,
circling tribes, possibly that he's seen enough in terms of treatment.
We're going to change it.
We're going to begin with the organization, and we're going to move to the 6th.
Very right.
Thank you.
I don't think they would show up.
So, the question is on that extra peg extension.
Do you have a motion?
Like, motion we approve?
Yes.
Is that I?
Williams?
Hi.
So, go.
And then, Marker.
Marker.
He is, also, Master of Remis, from professional service.
I'm going to do some credit.
You get me sorry.
I'm going to not do anything.
That's a good make it to money.
So, let's go to everything you know.
So, the first Master of Service Agreement between
IMA and Olsen was in 2016.
So, we're just doing a good five-year-old.
I think the only thing is changed is the work order option,
which is the same thing that's in the agreement with Anderson.
All of us forward to it.
So, getting out of the question, we'll try.
That's pretty much the same thing.
So, you're going to do that, Jane.
Or, for the P.O.s.
First, small projects, basically, we can just do the P.O.
of hurdles to get us around it.
Since our bakery is out of a quick state step, things like that.
It just helps us get to work quicker.
Is there a dollar mountain?
Yeah.
What is the 10-15 in this small?
No, there's the 21.
Whatever is in the first state policy.
Basically, whatever is in the first state policy,
the first state policy is referenced again in the NSA.
That was most of the comment that all of us had for us.
It was following the first state policy.
No, the else was changing in the area.
No.
I don't know what to do with it.
Everyone you want to be good for it.
I was flying over the last one.
It's just, we've been asked a couple times for it.
So, we went ahead and just, I mean, it's just a little bit more work than that.
So, give us some background on what sort of future providing force if we don't want it.
Right now.
Just in general, the most of it is limited tone that you still decide.
Street or so, there's a lot of housework, which is important.
Great for you all.
So, mostly, if you don't get on the road, so we're doing some climate placement stuff on the electric side.
We're doing some waterline projects.
We have no doubt until the relocations.
That's really what we have going on right now.
There's some older waterline design projects that we worked on.
Kind of started that around 19 or 20.
And then, of course, they did during COVID and prices were ridiculous on the scale of time.
So, they got shelled and now we're trying to bring those back around.
So, I'm going to talk about those.
See if we can do a reclead to get those construction costs down some and get them back out on the street.
So, as the reason that we're using you as a vendor is for expertise.
Then, act here.
Sure, background knowledge history. Yes, all of that down. Okay, and resources. Yes
What would it look like Tyler if we didn't use these folks?
Oh, yeah, I have an in-house engineer. Which are we hard because you know we have electric with water sewer
We have streets and you really have an engineer that would have all those different.
For one day, you couldn't Sam. I don't know if I didn't know that engineer could Sam electrical or sewer.
I can't civil. I'm a civil. But we have a lot of electrical in our office.
I don't because I'm on the civil side, so street water sewer.
It's half the fine one person that can do that works at me.
And I just ask so that people have a original understanding of what the purpose of your service is.
Right. I'm going to an electrical consultant around here. There's only two or three of us really.
Is the gentleman you grow in? He's only electrical side. He's going to talk to you in the next one.
Yeah, he's going to talk to you in the next one.
But if you're waiting, he's not waiting. He's chasing.
He's waiting for anybody that's on that.
He's waiting for somebody.
He keeps you as his pants.
This is the same top sort of.
Is that Anderson Rod's color?
And this isn't even any. Yes, yes.
We have a master agreement that I got with Anderson.
So there's no dollars with this.
There's no soap with this.
This is basically the boiler plate.
We had seven agreement.
And we're all just agreeing on this is the way that we're going to work with each other.
And then when a project comes up, we come back.
We talk about it. We put together a soap.
And it costs to do that work.
And then we're going to come back to talk to you again.
Which is what Jason's going to do on the next action.
This just has all that background.
That's to it.
So when we start talking about projects, we have all the legal stuff over here.
And now it's just, this is what the project is.
And this is what it's going to cost.
Do you need to do the engineering portion of it.
Turn it over.
I'll use construction.
Yeah.
So any waterline that we've been out.
We have to have a permanent duty cues.
We have to have an engineer design and seal it.
So we've got hydraulic model already for the town.
So we'll just keep adding it.
I had to swap lines up, I had to step up.
Is it also the same thing that you wanted to come in here?
I'm sorry.
Yes, sir.
I'm going to do like you're doing.
They do not do like you're doing.
So what makes you decide to do you pick or to different zones?
So you have water on it that you're going to do.
What makes you pick?
Well, those are projects that they have been about locations.
And so, most of them ask somebody that works for a guide.
Like, what is the term for?
The same thing I was for you all.
With the city engineer, we had one of them that would go not in the same way.
So you know, trying to get to send.
Basically, we can just call them a massive amount of process.
It's a worse amount of time.
That's the 69-8 in project.
We're going to talk about that a little bit.
That was, which we were already here when that one came through.
So we had the background to it, but we wanted to be able to move on it.
The water line projects that we met on I've already seen them.
They were also designed originally.
We're just trying to move them somewhere else.
Maybe make it a little easier to do that.
You know, the question about that?
I don't know.
For a movie.
Come on.
to say 10% funding for the whole team,
the right way are they private?
So they're private easement, and we, as part of this,
again, we're buying private easement.
That is our thing that's not going back in private easement,
because otherwise, if you have to relocate the new paper
to talk to us, I guess that a part of this will work
within the bottom, purchase the private easement.
Part of the location.
Does that, that private easement in person to the team?
Yeah, certainly, but once this is a great tonight,
we're going back in private easement.
Is there a theory of this project? Is there a thing that's already on this field?
It's a thing that's coming out of the email.
I don't understand how to understand that.
Is that because of the grant funding that they use?
It's just that for so long, this started in the 2021.
The field being was almost three years ago now.
Yeah.
And we're going to do a good thing.
Yeah, it just took a couple years to get through the utility coordinator to figure out what we were doing.
I actually moved the line for more than a day originally wanted it,
because it was going over buildings.
This is just coordination right now.
They had some turnover with their project manager on the utility coordination side.
I think it fell in a crack for a while.
Oh, that did it.
The utility guy.
I see that.
It's probably the first one.
It's probably kind of the old one.
Like if you're going.
Of course I'm saying.
Okay.
Right there.
There were cracks, basically.
Yeah.
It used to 69.
If you thought it was always out in the country, they'd quite a little bit.
Actually, yeah.
I think they'll probably do that.
Yeah.
The project runs very cold.
You're cold.
You can say that.
But we're going to stop the tracks.
That's where you're all.
The game, because it's in the easement.
It's 100% reimbursed.
The counties already reviewed it.
So.
Yes.
Can't you reimbursed?
Right.
We were.
We were on the dinner chain.
But this is this is some prior.
I.
Worker that it was a state reimbursement.
You know, but it's gone through the county.
So we're going to reimbursed for the purchase of the.
Yes.
We went from that.
And that.
It's.
This is.
That's.
But.
It was.
Yeah.
This.
What does.
I mean.
Maybe.
It's.
The.
Yeah.
This.
That.
It's the same size, I mean it's the same size, all the same size conductor,
we're just moving it into new needs, to get it out of the way.
is it existing transformers in the middle of the world?
Any other questions on that?
Say it.
I'll go on.
In step two.
The state.
The session chart?
I don't know.
Perfect.
I don't even know what it is.
Well, during the plans for the C.C.
We've got a 15A, a circle of being underground,
or a 60.
Say how we six on A.
How we can, waterline, relocation,
and an amount of 2,566 dollars.
And the question is,
and that's a negative number.
So it's actually a defect.
Do you want a group?
No.
And again, it's, it's another, it's a 100% reimbursement.
Through a lot.
I'm working with Tyler trying to work through a bit.
Sorry.
The reimbursement.
It's been up through.
I just, I need your all signature for it.
Since the construction contract is between,
MSUA and Circle B.
We're going to work on two change over the real time.
I'm not sure what I'm playing with.
This actually, which means it actually worked out great.
18T relocated to head of us and got labor right.
And it asked how we was right next to 18T.
And so there was nowhere left.
Yeah.
There was nowhere left for the waterline.
So actually loaded it back in the existing case.
They cut the ends off of it.
They unloaded it.
They swapped it out.
And so because they didn't place new casing under the road,
we just extended it on the one side to get it out of the right way.
Which we talked about doing it one time.
We just didn't know if we could shut the water all that long.
But it was spying at another well back up and running by.
And so.
Yeah.
So you said we're going to go 18T?
What?
You're saying you're going to go 18T?
It does.
I don't get a car block.
Just clarify.
18T didn't know what you think about that as a comment.
I think most of you too approve.
Yeah.
But I was clear.
He's dead.
Thanks.
13.
14.
and B-Wavours, and my own towers, now the authority, and my own towers, I think the authority for the Rimao,
the remodeling, the remodeling, and my own towers for the Rimao C mange and I have arrived to a five-piece Rimao C.
Yes, this is the B-Wavours for the Rimao C.
There we are in the Loth container, and I am so say a P.E.
It's not just exceed 10,000, 441 more than 90 hours, and the same thing for non-trients,
non-trients, it's an extensive job, but it's just more of a MVP-plugging support.
Mine powers will be MVP.
They gotta say, why is actually getting it right now for this C8?
So this is the continuation of the discussion we had in the workshop,
and what we had discussed at that time, and this was the follow-up that we do at the beginning of the episode.
Who was the Delano man, and there was a window wreck.
10,000 dollars, but there was also a time when at the time, I always stand through the time building for it expires.
The way it works is hard.
They need...
They need an extension.
Thank you.
They're probably going to need that whole year.
They're going to need that whole year.
I mean, I guess we can ask the crew now, or we'll get it back.
That's the extension.
Okay.
Sorry, I'm sorry.
Again, this is going to be a total gathering of all of that.
Everyone wants to be excited.
This was really like 14 months.
Somewhere in that course there.
And at the end of that, if they need more time than that,
we'll just have to have to have a good new real improvement.
So hopefully, by that time, it should be within the cosmetic stages.
And so, you know, it really wasn't easy to find a part of the mechanism.
And that you're paying trams like that.
This is really perfect.
This is more of an option.
You can find it when you make the ADA.
Why didn't borrow all the hallways?
We'll be less room soon.
It's the time now that those things aren't getting in.
It's going to be more than 14 months.
41 more than that.
We'll take that whole year, nine tribes, it's more of a region of the plumbing,
some electrical, or a huge shaft that runs down the middle of each side.
All plumbing, electrical, heat nearies in that shaft.
The longer it makes it, we're doing this, it's a game, all of the communities that came
with electrical.
We're going to have a cabinet, well, that's not made yet, but they don't know what we need
to do about it, so I don't know what I'm going to do, but I don't know what I'm going to do.
I'm going to do a little bit of a system, yeah.
Do you have any questions for grabs?
I'm going to go a little closer.
Motion to a broom.
It's good.
Thank you.
A little bit.
Now I think that's the right.
I think that's the right.
Thank you.
All right.
You're welcome.
It's a great opportunity.
Alright.
of out of four from the regular G and my ancestral and public facilities of the
local police, five, five, five, five, four of mine, four of us.
Let's say, purple, and bear five, and four of us.
This is five, no?
The green being never, I'm five.
I don't know if I'd like to leave.
I'd like to leave.
Yeah, friends, as high.
five, five, five, five, five, four.